A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Leadership Development Program (LDP), Accession 2017:027 FA1298
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Southeast Region LDP Fellow files, 1960-1979; 4; 19.36 Cubic Feet About 39 LTR size Hollinger boxes and 5 LGL size Hollinger boxes
  - G-M, 1966-1978; 2; 8.25 Cubic Feet About 18.75 LTR size Hollinger boxes
    - Hinson, Dorothy J. - Hayneville, Alabama, 1972-1973 (Box 58, Folder 813)
    - Hinson, Dorothy J. - Hayneville, Alabama, 1972-1975 (Box 58, Folder 814-815)
    - Huffman, Rufus C. - Union Springs, Alabama, 1966-1971; File includes an untitled still image (Folder 817). (Box 59, Folder 816-819)
    - Huffman, Rufus C. - Union Springs, Alabama, 1967-1972; File includes a set of five still images depicting the Workshop on the Role of Visual Aids in the Individualization of Instruction (Folder 820). (Box 59, Folder 820-821)
    - Hunt (nee Hill), Cellestine V. - Albany, Georgia, 1971-1973 (Box 59, Folder 822)
      Within the file, materials refer to Leadership Development Program Fellow Cellestine V. Hunt by her married name (Cellestine V. Hunt), by her maiden name (Cellestine V. Hill), and by the name Cellestine H. Hunt.
    - Hunt (nee Hill), Cellestine V. - Albany, Georgia, 1972-1974 (Box 59, Folder 823)
    - Jackson, Annie B. - Hayneville, Alabama, 1972-1973 (Box 60, Folder 824)
    - Jackson, Annie B. - Hayneville, Alabama, 1971-1975 (Box 60, Folder 825-826)
    - Jankovic, Joanne F. - LaGrange, Georgia, 1970-1976 (Box 60, Folder 827-828)
    - Jankovic, Joanne F. - LaGrange, Georgia, 1970-1972 (Box 60, Folder 829)
    - Jernigan, Curtis D. - Union Springs, Alabama, 1969-1975 (Box 60, Folder 830-831)
    - Jernigan, Curtis D. - Union Springs, Alabama, 1969-1971 (Box 60, Folder 832)
    - Jimmie, Irma A. - Philadelphia, Mississippi, 1970-1974 (Box 60, Folder 833)
    - Jimmie, Irma A. - Philadelphia, Mississippi, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 834)
    - Johnson, David A. - Butler, Alabama, 1970-1973 (Box 61, Folder 835)
    - Johnson, David A. - Butler, Alabama, 1970-1973 (Box 61, Folder 836)
    - Jefferson, Cynthia A. - Atlanta, Georgia, 1971-1975 (Box 61, Folder 837)
    - Johnson, Ida L. - Columbia, South Carolina, 1972-1973 (Box 61, Folder 838)
    - Johnson, Ida L. - Columbia, South Carolina, 1972-1974 (Box 61, Folder 839)
    - Johnson, Lillie Jean - Georgetown, South Carolina, 1969-1971 (Box 61, Folder 840)
    - Johnson, Lillie Jean - Georgetown, South Carolina, 1969-1971 (Box 61, Folder 841)
    - Johnson, Toreatha - Butler, Alabama, 1967-1975 (Box 61, Folder 842-843)
    - Johnson, Toreatha - Butler, Alabama, 1967-1975 (Box 61, Folder 844)
      1. Johnson, Mrs. Toreatha -- Reports
    - Jolley, Freddie G. - Pelahatchie, Mississippi, 1971-1977 (Box 61, Folder 845-846)
    - Jolley, Freddie G. - Pelahatchie, Mississippi, 1972-1973 (Box 62, Folder 847)
    - Jones, Aaron - Pascagoula, Mississippi, 1970-1977; File inludes an untitled still image of a young girl (Folder 848). (Box 62, Folder 848-849)
    - Jones, Aaron - Pascagoula, Mississippi, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 850)
    - Jones, Evelyn - Forsyth, Georgia, 1966-1969 (Box 62, Folder 851-852)
    - Jones, Evelyn - Forsyth, Georgia, 1967-1974 (Box 62, Folder 853)
    - Jones, Herbert - Braxton, Mississippi, 1970-1971 (Box 62, Folder 854)
    - Jones, Lavaree - Jackson, Mississippi, 1972-1973 (Box 62, Folder 855-856)
    - Jones, Lavaree - Jackson, Mississippi, 1972-1974 (Box 62, Folder 857-858)
    - Judge, Walter Wallace - Albany, Georgia, 1966-1975 (Box 62, Folder 859-861)
    - Judge, Walter Wallace - Albany, Georgia, 1967-1973 (Box 63, Folder 862)
    - Kahn, Si - LaGrange, Georgia, 1969-1977; File includes a still image of LDP Fellow Si Kahn (Folder 863). (Box 63, Folder 863-866)
    - Kahn, Si - LaGrange, Georgia, 1969-1974 (Box 63, Folder 867-869)
    - Kahn, Si - LaGrange, Georgia, 1969-1978 (Box 63, Folder 870)
    - Kandel, Harris - Cornelia, Georgia, 1967-1971 (Box 63, Folder 871-872)
    - Kandel, Harris - Cornelia, Georgia, 1968-1970 (Box 63, Folder 873)
    - Keebler, Glenn - Lumber City, Georgia, 1971-1974 (Box 64, Folder 874)
    - Keebler, Glenn - Lumber City, Georgia, 1971-1974 (Box 64, Folder 875)
    - Kibler, Gilford - Huntsville, Alabama, 1975-1977 (Box 64, Folder 876-877)
      Within the original folder, another folder marked "Gilford Kibler -- 1975-1976" had been inserted to become part of the overall file.
    - Kidd, Jeanell E. - Meridian, Mississippi, 1974-1976 (Box 64, Folder 878-879)
      Within the original folder, another folder marked "Jeanell Kidd -- 74-75" had been inserted to become part of the overall file.
    - King, Frankie B. - Auburn, Alabama, 1973-1974 (Box 64, Folder 880)
    - King, Frankie B. - Auburn, Alabama, 1973-1975 (Box 64, Folder 881-882)
    - Kirksey, Reverend Peter J. - Boligee, Alabama, 1967-1972 (Box 64, Folder 883)
    - Kirksey, Reverend Peter J. - Boligee, Alabama, 1966-1972; File includes a set of three untitled still images. (Box 64, Folder 884)
      Within the original folder, another folder marked "Kirksey, R. J. (Rev.) -- (Green County, Alabama)" had been inserted to become part of the overall file.
    - Knox, Kathleen R. - Rock Hills, South Carolina, 1970-1976 (Box 65, Folder 885-886)
    - Knox, Kathleen R. - Rock Hills, South Carolina, 1971-1972 (Box 65, Folder 887)
    - Ladson, Abie - Georgetown, South Carolina, 1969-1976 (Box 65, Folder 888-890)
    - Ladson, Abie and Tommy Shubrick, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 891)
      File contains documents related to Abie Ladson and fellow former LDP Fellow Tommy Shubrick's Post Fellowship Supplement research proposal.
    - Ladson, Abie - Georgetown, South Carolina, 1969-1974 (Box 65, Folder 892)
    - Lester, Louise R. - Florence, South Carolina, 1968-1973 (Box 65, Folder 893-894)
    - Lester, Louise R. - Florence, South Carolina, 1968-1973 (Box 65, Folder 895)
    - Lester, Willie F. - Mitchell, Georgia, 1971-1975 (Box 66, Folder 896-897)
    - Lester, Willie F. - Mitchell, Georgia, 1972-1973 (Box 66, Folder 898)
    - Linker, Larry C. - Atlanta, Georgia, 1970-1976 (Box 66, Folder 899-901)
    - Linker, Larry C. - Atlanta, Georgia, 1970-1973 (Box 66, Folder 902)
    - Long, Willie B. - Greenville, Mississippi, 1970-1972 (Box 66, Folder 903)
    - Long, Willie B. - Greenville, Mississippi, 1969-1975 (Box 66, Folder 904-905)
    - Love, Leon A. - York, South Carolina, 1973-1975 (Box 66, Folder 906-907)
    - Love, Leon A. - York, South Carolina, 1973-1974 (Box 66, Folder 908)
    - Lyles, John H. - Columbia, South Carolina, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 909)
    - Mack, Mary Y. - Mobile, Alabama, 1968-1970 (Box 67, Folder 910)
    - Mack, Mary Y. - Mobile, Alabama, 1967-1975 (Box 67, Folder 911-912)
    - Macklin, Harriet J. - Atlanta, Georgia, 1975-1976 (Box 67, Folder 913)
      Within the original folder, another folder marked "H. J. Macklin -- 1975-6" had been inserted to become part of the overall file.
    - Manning, Selene - Tuskegee Institute, Alabama, 1969-1971 (Box 67, Folder 914)
    - Manning, Selene - Tuskegee Institute, Alabama, 1969-1975 (Box 67, Folder 915-916)
    - Mants, Robert, Jr. - Albany, Georgia, 1971-1972 (Box 67, Folder 917)
    - Mants, Robert, Jr. - Albany, Georgia, 1972-1973 (Box 67, Folder 918)
      Original folder was marked "Bob Mants: Post Fellowship Supplement"
    - Mants, Robert, Jr. - Albany, Georgia, 1971-1975 (Box 67, Folder 919-922)
    - Matthews, Marcus - Florence, South Carolina, 1970-1972 (Box 68, Folder 923)
    - Matthews, Marcus - Florence, South Carolina, circa 1971-1972 (Box 68, Folder 924)
      Original folder was marked "Marcus Matthews - Post Fellowship Supplement".
    - Matthews, Marcus - Florence, South Carolina, 1970-1974 (Box 68, Folder 925-927)
    - Mazyck, Rubystene I. - Cross, South Carolina, 1972-1975 (Box 68, Folder 928-929)
    - Mazyck, Rubystene I. - Cross, South Carolina, 1973-1974 (Box 68, Folder 930)
    - McCarty, Jennie B. - Greenwood, Mississippi, 1968-1975 (Box 68, Folder 931)
    - McCarty, Jennie B. - Greenwood, Mississippi, 1968-1970 (Box 68, Folder 932)
    - McCoy, Barbara - Greenville, Mississippi, 1974-1975 (Box 68, Folder 933-934)
      Within the original folder, another folder marked "Barbara McCoy -- 74-75" had been inserted to become part of the overall file.
    - McDuffie, Dorothy J. - Florence, South Carolina, 1974-1976 (Box 68, Folder 935-936)
    - McDuffie, Dorothy J. - Florence, South Carolina, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 937)
    - McElhannon, William S. - Jackson, Mississippi, 1972-1973 (Box 69, Folder 938)
    - McElhannon, William S. - Jackson, Mississippi, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 939)
    - McElhannon, William S. - Jackson, Mississippi, 1971-1973 (Box 69, Folder 940)
    - McLaurin, Charles - Cleveland, Mississippi, 1973-1975 (Box 69, Folder 941-942)
      Within the original folder, another folder marked "Charles McLaurin -- 74-75" had been inserted to become part of the overall file.
    - McTeer, Vidalia G. - Orangeburg, South Carolina, 1969-1977 (Box 69, Folder 943-944)
    - McTeer, Vidalia G. - Orangeburg, South Carolina, 1970-1973 (Box 69, Folder 945)
    - Miller, Evelyn H. - Florence, South Carolina, 1974-1975 (Box 69, Folder 946-947)
      Within the original folder, another folder marked "Evelyn Miller -- 74-75" had been inserted to become part of the overall file.
    - Mims, Howell G. - Caledonia, Mississippi, 1969-1974 (Box 69, Folder 948-949)
    - Mims, Howell G. - Caledonia, Mississippi, 1969-1971 (Box 69, Folder 950)
    - Mitchell, Curtis - Phenix City, Alabama, 1969-1977 (Box 70, Folder 951-952)
    - Mitchell, Curtis - Phenix City, Alabama, 1969-1975 (Box 70, Folder 953)
    - Mitchell, Willie P. - Newman, Georgia, 1970-1972 (Box 70, Folder 954)
    - Mitchell, Willie P. - Newman, Georgia, 1970-1972 (Box 70, Folder 955)
    - Mizell, Patricia B. - Columbia, South Carolina, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 956)
    - Monroe, Dorothy M. - Thomasville, Georgia, 1967-1975 (Box 70, Folder 957-958)
    - Monroe, Dorothy M. - Thomasville, Georgia, 1967-1970 (Box 70, Folder 959)
    - Montgomery, Dexter W. - Amory, Mississippi, 1972-1977 (Box 71, Folder 960-962)
    - Montgomery, Dexter W. - Amory, Mississippi, 1973-1975 (Box 71, Folder 963)
    - Moody, Cecil - Conyers, Georgia, 1966-1979 (Box 71, Folder 964-965)
    - Moody, Cecil - Conyers, Georgia, 1967-1972 (Box 71, Folder 966)
    - Moore, Yvonne - Smithdale, Mississippi, 1971-1973 (Box 71, Folder 967)
    - Moore, Yvonne - Smithdale, Mississippi, 1971-1977 (Box 71, Folder 968-969)
    - Morgan, Bobby L. - Fayetteville, Arkansas, 1969-1975 (Box 71, Folder 970)
    - Morgan, Bobby L. - Fayetteville, Arkansas, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 971)
    - Morrison, Charles R. - Rome, Georgia, 1966-1969 (Box 72, Folder 972)
      LDP Fellow, short-term award: 1967-1968
    - Morrison, Charles R. - Rome, Georgia, 1966-1968 (Box 72, Folder 973)
    - Myatt, Robert - Manson, North Carolina, 1974-1975 (Box 72, Folder 974)
      Within the original folder, another folder marked "Robert Myatt -- 74-75" had been inserted to become part of the overall file.
  - N-S, 1966-1978; 3; 3.63 Cubic Feet About 4.25 LTR size Hollinger boxes and 4 LGL size Hollinger boxes
    Subseries contains Fellow files for Southeast Region Leadership Development Program Fellows whose last names begin with the letters N-S.
    - Neville, Sidney B. - Hahira, Georgia, 1966-1975 (Box 72, Folder 975)
    - Neville, Sidney B. - Hahira, Georgia, 1967-1972 (Box 72, Folder 976)
    - Nolley, Lenora P. - Warrenton, Georgia, 1970-1971 (Box 72, Folder 977)
    - Nolley, Lenora P. - Warrenton, Georgia, 1967-1971 (Box 72, Folder 978)
    - O'Korley, Seth M. - Fairfield, Alabama, 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 979)
    - O'Korley, Seth M. - Fairfield, Alabama, 1969-1976 (Box 72, Folder 980-982)
      Within the original folder, another folder marked "Seth Okorley" had been inserted to become part of the overall file.
    - Palmer, Mary Lee - Calhoun, Georgia, 1972-1976 (Box 72, Folder 983-984)
    - Palmer, Mary Lee - Calhoun, Georgia, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 985)
      Original folder was marked "Mary Lee Palmer -- Post Fellowship Supplement"
    - Palmer, Mary Lee - Calhoun, Georgia, 1972-1973 (Box 73, Folder 986)
    - Parker, Marshall E. - Conway, South Carolina, 1968-1969 (Box 73, Folder 987)
    - Parker, Marshall E. - Conway, South Carolina, 1967-1970 (Box 73, Folder 988-990)
    - Patterson, Louise W. - LaGrange, Georgia, 1966-1976 (Box 73, Folder 991)
    - Patterson, Louise W. - LaGrange, Georgia, 1967-1975 (Box 73, Folder 992)
    - Perkins, Reverend John M. - Mendehall, Mississippi, 1972-1974 (Box 73, Folder 993)
    - Perkins, Reverend John M. - Mendehall, Mississippi, 1972-1977 (Box 73, Folder 994-995)
    - Peterson, Terrance K. - Cross, South Carolina, 1971-1977 (Box 73, Folder 996-998)
    - Peterson, Terrance K. - Cross, South Carolina, 1971-1974 (Box 74, Folder 999)
    - Poole, Claudia F. - Montgomery, Alabama, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 1000)
    - Poole, Claudia F. - Montgomery, Alabama, 1969-1977; File includes a still image of LDP Fellow Claudia F. Poole. (Box 74, Folder 1001)
    - Poston, Joe T. - Waterloo, Alabama, 1967-1977 (Box 74, Folder 1002-1004)
    - Poston, Joe T. - Waterloo, Alabama, 1970-1973 (Box 74, Folder 1005)
    - Poston, Thomas R. - Columbia, South Carolina, 1969-1976; File includes a still image of LDP Fellow Thomas (Brad) Poston (Folder 1006). (Box 74, Folder 1006-1007)
      Within the file, materials generally refer to Leadership Development Program Fellow Thomas R. Poston as Brad Poston.
    - Poston, Thomas R. - Columbia, South Carolina, 1969-1972 (Box 74, Folder 1008)
    - Purnell, Michael - Luthersville, Georgia, 1972-1977 (Box 75, Folder 1009)
    - Purnell, Michael - Luthersville, Georgia, 1973-1978 (Box 75, Folder 1010)
    - Rhodes, Alfred H., Jr. - Jackson, Mississippi, 1970-1977 (Box 75, Folder 1011-1013)
      Within the original folder, another folder marked "Al Rhodes - Tri-County Comm. Center" had been inserted to become part of the overall file.
      File includes materials related to Martha J. A. Heggins, a different Leadership Development Program Fellow. Heggins' Fellow files are located within Folders 800-804.
    - Rhodes, Alfred H., Jr. - Jackson, Mississippi, 1970-1971 (Box 75, Folder 1014)
    - Richmond, Reverend Isaac, Jr. - Frogmore, South Carolina, 1969-1975 (Box 75, Folder 1015-1016)
      Within the original folder, another folder marked "Post Fellowship Supplement Proposal - Isaac Richmond" had been inserted to become part of the overall file.
    - Richmond, Reverend Isaac, Jr. - Frogmore, South Carolina, 1969-1976; File includes a still image of Reverend Isaac Richmond Jr. (Folder 1017). (Box 75, Folder 1017-1020)
      Within the original folder, another folder marked "Isaac Richmond - Post Fellowship Proposal 8/30/71" had been inserted to become part of the overall file.
    - Robertson, Wilbur - LaGrange, Georgia, 1969-1974; File includes still image of LDP Fellow Wilbur Robertson (Folder 1021). (Box 76, Folder 1021-1022)
    - Robertson, Wilbur - LaGrange, Georgia, 1969-1971 (Box 76, Folder 1023)
    - Robinson, Randolph W. - Lorman, Mississippi, 1972-1973 (Box 76, Folder 1024)
    - Robinson, Randolph W. - Lorman, Mississippi, 1971-1974 (Box 76, Folder 1025)
    - Robinson, Will M. - Jackson, Mississippi, 1975-1976 (Box 76, Folder 1026-1027)
      Within the original folder, another folder marked "Will M. Robinson" had been inserted to become part of the overall file.
    - Rudolph, Annie P. - Montgomery, Alabama, 1968-1970 (Box 76, Folder 1028)
    - Rudolph, Annie P. - Montgomery, Alabama, 1967-1975 (Box 76, Folder 1029-1030)
    - Rudolph, Jesse J. - Georgetown, South Carolina, 1969-1977; File includes a still image of LDP Fellow Jesse J. Rudolph (Folder 1031). (Box 76, Folder 1031-1032)
    - Rudolph, Jesse J. - Georgetown, South Carolina, 1969-1970 (Box 76, Folder 1033)
    - Scholes, F. Wade - Powder Springs, Georgia, 1972-1973 (Box 77, Folder 1034)
    - Scholes, F. Wade - Powder Springs, Georgia, 1971-1976; File includes an untitled still image (Folder 1038). (Box 77, Folder 1035-1038)
      Within the original folder, another folder marked "F. Wade Scholes -- First and Second Expense Reports" had been inserted to become part of the overall file.
    - Seabury, Sandra L. - Jackson, Mississippi, 1973-1976 (Box 77, Folder 1039-1040)
    - Seabury, Sandra L. - Jackson, Mississippi, 1973-1975 (Box 77, Folder 1041)
    - Shubrick, Tommy T. - Georgetown, South Carolina, 1969-1978 (Box 77, Folder 1042-1043)
      An untitled still image has been removed from the file (Folder 1042) for stabilization.
    - Shubrick, Tommy T. - Georgetown, South Carolina, 1969-1972 (Box 77, Folder 1044)
    - Smith, Charles - Calhoun, Alabama, 1970-1972 (Box 77, Folder 1045)
    - Smith, Charles - Calhoun, Alabama, 1967-1977 (Box 78, Folder 1046)
    - Smith, Cooper A. - Gaffney, South Carolina, 1969-1977; File includes a still image of LDP Fellow Cooper A. Smith (Folder 1047). (Box 78, Folder 1047-1048)
    - Smith, Cooper A. - Gaffney, South Carolina, 1969-1975 (Box 78, Folder 1049)
    - Smith, Johnny Elmer - Estill, South Carolina, 1968-1969 (Box 78, Folder 1050)
    - Smith, Johnny Elmer - Estill, South Carolina, 1967-1970 (Box 78, Folder 1051-1052)
    - Smith, Nathaniel E.- Union Springs, Alabama, 1971-1975 (Box 78, Folder 1053-1054)
    - Smith, Nathaniel E. - Union Springs, Alabama, 1973-1974 (Box 78, Folder 1055)
    - Stephens, Augustus T., Jr. - Aiken, South Carolina, 1970-1975 (Box 78, Folder 1056-1057)
    - Stephens, Augustus T., Jr. - Aiken, South Carolina, 1971-1973 (Box 79, Folder 1058)
    - Stover, James W., Jr. - Sumter, South Carolina, 1967-1970 (Box 79, Folder 1059)
    - Stover, James W., Jr. - Sumter, South Carolina, 1968-1970 (Box 79, Folder 1060)
    - Sutton, Donald C. - Greenville, Mississippi, 1973-1974 (Box 79, Folder 1061)
    - Sutton, Donald C. - Greenville, Mississippi, 1973-1977 (Box 79, Folder 1062)
    - Swans, Sandra L. - Atlanta, Georgia, 1972-1976 (Box 79, Folder 1063-1064)
    - Swans, Sandra L. - Atlanta, Georgia, 1972-1974 (Box 79, Folder 1065)
  - T-Z, 1963-1979; 4; 3.74 Cubic Feet About 7.5 LTR size Hollinger boxes and 1 LGL size Hollinger box
    Subseries contains Fellow files for Southeast Region Leadership Development Program Fellows whose last names begin with the letters T-Z.
    - Taylor, James Calvin - Florence, South Carolina, 1967-1976 (Box 79, Folder 1066-1068)
    - Taylor, James Calvin - Florence, South Carolina, 1967-1971 (Box 79, Folder 1069-1070)
    - Terry, Connie H. - Orangeburg, South Carolina, 1963-1970 (Box 80, Folder 1071-1072)
      File contains a copy of James Baldwin's "A Talk to Teachers". The piece includes excerpts from a talk Baldwin gave to New York City teachers on October 16, 1963. The Saturday Review originally published it on December 21, 1963.
    - Terry, Connie H. - Orangeburg, South Carolina, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 1073)
    - Thompson, Bennie G. - Bolton, Mississippi, 1974-1976 (Box 80, Folder 1074)
      Within the original folder, another folder marked "Bennie Thompson -- 74-75" had been inserted to become part of the overall file.
    - Thompson, James R. - Silas, Alabama, 1967-1969 (Box 80, Folder 1075)
    - Thompson, James R. - Silas, Alabama, 1967-1969 (Box 80, Folder 1076)
    - Thompson, Leonard E. - Oxford, Mississippi, 1968-1979 (Box 80, Folder 1077)
    - Thompson, Leonard E. - Oxford, Mississippi, 1968-1970 (Box 80, Folder 1078)
    - Toporek, Robert - Charleston, South Carolina, 1970-1978 (Box 80, Folder 1079-1082)
      An audio recording titled Report II by Robert Toporek has been removed from the file (folder 1079) for stabilization.
      This item has been assigned the unique separation number 2017:027:046 and is listed below.
      - Report II by Robert Toporek, 2017:027:046
        Special format items have been separated from the above listed file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
        Conditions Governing Access
        Access to item is restricted pending audio stabilization.
    - Toporek, Robert - Charleston, South Carolina, 1970-1973 (Box 81, Folder 1083)
    - Underwood, Lawrence Eugene - LaGrange, Georgia, 1967-1972 (Box 81, Folder 1084)
    - Underwood, Lawrence Eugene - LaGrange, Georgia, 1966-1974 (Box 81, Folder 1085)
    - Ward, Bettye J. - Brandon, Mississippi, 1972-1976 (Box 81, Folder 1086-1087)
    - Ward, Bettye J. - Brandon, Mississippi, 1972-1974 (Box 81, Folder 1088)
    - Ward, Hattie V. - Prentiss, Mississippi, 1967-1974; File includes a set of five still images titled Hattie Ward photographs. (Box 81, Folder 1089)
      1. Ward, Hattie V. – Reports
    - Ward, Hattie V. - Prentiss, Mississippi, 1967-1974; File includes a set of three still images that were attached to a letter LDP Fellow Hattie V. Ward sent to Dorothy Hassfeld on April 1, 1968 (Folder 1094). (Box 81, Folder 1090-1094)
      File includes an envelope addressed to the Leadership Development Program from LDP Fellow Hattie V. Ward. This envelope contains craft projects and other types of student work from a first grade elementary school class.
      There are also two drawings that Ward likely created. These items were sealed in an envelope marked "Ward, Miscellaneous".
      An untitled still image has been removed from the file (Folder 1092) for stabilization.
    - Ward, Michael C. - Greenville, Mississippi, 1972-1976 (Box 82, Folder 1095-1096)
    - Ward, Michael C. - Greenville, Mississippi, 1973-1975 (Box 82, Folder 1097)
    - Warren, Ralph W. - Sparta, Georgia, 1973-1976 (Box 82, Folder 1098-1099)
    - Warren, Ralph W. - Sparta, Georgia, 1973-1974 (Box 82, Folder 1100)
    - Washington, David W. - Pace, Mississippi, 1973-1977 (Box 82, Folder 1101)
    - Washington, Martha L. - Wetumpka, Alabama, 1969-1976; File includes a still image of LDP Fellow Martha L. Washington (Folder 1102). (Box 82, Folder 1102-1103)
    - Washington, Martha L. - Wetumpka, Alabama, 1971-1974 (Box 82, Folder 1104)
      Original folder was marked "Martha Washington -- Post Fellowship Supplement Proposal".
    - Washington, Martha L. - Wetumpka, Alabama, 1969-1974 (Box 82, Folder 1105)
    - Westcott, Robert S. - Rossville, Georgia, 1964-1975 (Box 83, Folder 1106-1107)
      An untitled still image has been removed from the file (Folder 1107) for stabilization.
    - Westcott, Robert S. - Rossville, Georgia, 1967-1972 (Box 83, Folder 1108)
    - White, Joseph, Jr. - Atlanta, Georgia, 1970-1974 (Box 83, Folder 1109)
    - White, Joseph, Jr. - Atlanta, Georgia, 1971-1974 (Box 83, Folder 1110-1111)
    - White, Clima J. - Tuskegee, Alabama, 1973-1976 (Box 83, Folder 1112-1113)
    - White, Clima J. - Tuskegee, Alabama, 1972-1978 (Box 83, Folder 1114-1117)
    - Whitney, Tom C. - Columbia, South Carolina, 1970-1973 (Box 84, Folder 1118)
    - Whitney, Tom C. - Columbia, South Carolina, 1970-1976 (Box 84, Folder 1119-1120)
    - Whitney, William B. - Columbia, South Carolina, 1970-1975 (Box 84, Folder 1121)
    - Whitney, William B. - Columbia, South Carolina, 1970-1974 (Box 84, Folder 1122)
    - Williams, Brenda J. - Camden, Alabama, 1972-1974 (Box 84, Folder 1123-1124)
      Within the original folder, another folder marked "Brenda Williams -- First and Second Expense Reports" had been inserted to become part of the overall file.
    - Williams, Brenda J. - Camden, Alabama, 1972-1974 (Box 84, Folder 1125)
    - Williams, Dorothy B. - Columbia, South Carolina, 1968-1969 (Box 84, Folder 1126)
    - Williams, Dorothy B. - Columbia, South Carolina, 1967-1970 (Box 84, Folder 1127-1128)
    - Williams, Freddie L. - Darlington, South Carolina, 1967-1977 (Box 85, Folder 1129-1131)
    - Williams, Freddie L. - Darlington, South Carolina, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 1132)